

ANSHUL CHAUDHARY

Passionate IT Student currently attending UNIVERSITY OF PETROLEUM AND ENERGY STUDIES with 2 years of learning and practising out new tools and technology stacks in the domain of BFSI specialisation (GPA 7.56) seeking for opportunities to use proven skills in the domains of web development and Java Software Development.

chaudharyanshul1407@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/raghav-kapoor-a81789185

+919837421121

github.com/anshulgit7

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of TechnologyUniversity Of Petroleum and Energy Studies

07/2018 - Present DEHRADUN

Computer Science

 Banking Financial Services and Insurance

12th

Dewan Public School

03/2017 - 03/2018

PCM

PhysicsChemistry

Mathematics

EXPERIENCE

CORE COMMITTEE - REGISTRATIONS Microsoft Technical Community

08/2018 - 08/2019 DEHRADUN

Responsibilities/Tasks

- Ensure that the mission and vision of MTC is followed.
- Maintaining the records of registrations

DATA ANALYST

Foxmula-The Smart Way

01/2019 - 03/2019

Responsibilities/Tasks

DEHRADUN

7.5

- I got exposed to various python Tools, Syntax and Libraries like numpy, pandas.
- Gained insights about how these libraries and tools are helpful for accessing and filtering of raw data.
- How to train a regression model and perform test cases on that.

ORGANIZATIONS

Microsoft Technical Community (08/2018 - 08/2019)

Foxmula - The Smart Way (01/2019 - 03/2019)

SKILLS

JAVA PROBLEM SOLVING DATA STRUCTURES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ALGORITHMS

FRONT END DEVELOPMENT CLOUD COMPUTING

OOPS SQL DBMS

PERSONAL PROJECTS

E-Medicos(Html + Css + Javasscript). (04/2020 - Present)

• A medical website to promote the govt medicinal business policies.

Decoding The Fittest Genomics From COVID-19 Survivors using Genetic Algorithms. (08/2020 - 12/2020)

Optimisation of Travelling Salesman Problem using Genetic Algorithms.(JAVA Language (01/2021 - Present)

CERTIFICATIONS

INTRODUCTION TO WEB DEVELOPMENT University of California

DATABASE ADMINISTRATION FUNDAMENTALS
Microsoft

BITS AND BYTES OF COMPUTER NETWORKING Google

JUNIOR PROJECT MANAGER

CLOUD COMPUTING BASICS
Learn Quest

ACHIEVEMENTS

GOLD BADGE PROGRAMMER ON HACKERRANK - JAVA

LANGUAGES

English
Full Professional Proficiency

French

Elementary Proficiency